[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"]}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "But what does this really mean in the context of the national election, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "does", "this", "really", "mean", "in", "the", "context", "of", "the", "national", "election", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I think it has an impact both on what's going to happen in the fall and more important what happens after that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "has", "an", "impact", "both", "on", "what", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "the", "fall", "and", "more", "important", "what", "happens", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"]}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I think the benefit of what happened on Tuesday was the power of ideas.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "benefit", "of", "what", "happened", "on", "Tuesday", "was", "the", "power", "of", "ideas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"], "LOCATION": ["Wisconsin"]}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "But if Romney called you and said, right, I've thought about this, you are my man, I presume you wouldn't turn him down?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "Romney", "called", "you", "and", "said", ",", "right", ",", "I", "'ve", "thought", "about", "this", ",", "you", "are", "my", "man", ",", "I", "presume", "you", "would", "n't", "turn", "him", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, again, I would probably eagerly persuade him that the best person in Wisconsin to put on the ticket is indeed Paul Ryan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "I", "would", "probably", "eagerly", "persuade", "him", "that", "the", "best", "person", "in", "Wisconsin", "to", "put", "on", "the", "ticket", "is", "indeed", "Paul", "Ryan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tonette"], "LOCATION": ["Wisconsin"]}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "He decides not Paul Ryan, it's going to be Scott Walker?", "question_tokens": ["He", "decides", "not", "Paul", "Ryan", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "Scott", "Walker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "ALKER: I think he'd have a pretty tough person to convince in terms of my wife, Tonette, after all this campaigning, all this focus in Wisconsin.", "answer_tokens": ["ALKER", ":", "I", "think", "he", "'d", "have", "a", "pretty", "tough", "person", "to", "convince", "in", "terms", "of", "my", "wife", ",", "Tonette", ",", "after", "all", "this", "campaigning", ",", "all", "this", "focus", "in", "Wisconsin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan", "Scott Walker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What do you make about this furor over President Clinton's comments, which have been, it appears, completely at odds with President Obama's positions in relation to Mitt Romney in particular and to the Bush tax cuts?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "about", "this", "furor", "over", "President", "Clinton", "'s", "comments", ",", "which", "have", "been", ",", "it", "appears", ",", "completely", "at", "odds", "with", "President", "Obama", "'s", "positions", "in", "relation", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "in", "particular", "and", "to", "the", "Bush", "tax", "cuts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, I think it -- you know, it's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton", "Obama", "Mitt Romney", "Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Is that accurate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "accurate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Is it really likely that he would have said these things which are so on the face of it, diametrically opposed to President Obama's main key election battle grounds as a mistake or could it be something a little bit more sinister?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "really", "likely", "that", "he", "would", "have", "said", "these", "things", "which", "are", "so", "on", "the", "face", "of", "it", ",", "diametrically", "opposed", "to", "President", "Obama", "'s", "main", "key", "election", "battle", "grounds", "as", "a", "mistake", "or", "could", "it", "be", "something", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "sinister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, I know his critics, not only Republican critics but even some of his Democratic critics see something a little bit more sinister.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "his", "critics", ",", "not", "only", "Republican", "critics", "but", "even", "some", "of", "his", "Democratic", "critics", "see", "something", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "sinister", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What was it like to see your son elected president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "to", "see", "your", "son", "elected", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Very emotional for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "emotional", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", ":", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You, as his friend, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["You", ",", "as", "his", "friend", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I think he felt badly for his son, and -- when his son was criticized.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "felt", "badly", "for", "his", "son", ",", "and", "--", "when", "his", "son", "was", "criticized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "?", "question_tokens": ["?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Chaz, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Chaz", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Well, I was just trying to think back to our last encounter, and what an extraordinary twist to your life that's gone on ever since.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "just", "trying", "to", "think", "back", "to", "our", "last", "encounter", ",", "and", "what", "an", "extraordinary", "twist", "to", "your", "life", "that", "'s", "gone", "on", "ever", "since", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "How much pressure did the fact that you decided to become a man -- how much pressure did that put on the relationship, do you think, looking back?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "pressure", "did", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "decided", "to", "become", "a", "man", "--", "how", "much", "pressure", "did", "that", "put", "on", "the", "relationship", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "looking", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I mean, I think it put some pressure on the relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "it", "put", "some", "pressure", "on", "the", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Did you feel that she ever fully embraced what you were doing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "that", "she", "ever", "fully", "embraced", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "You know, I think that she did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Do you regret doing that, with hindsight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "doing", "that", ",", "with", "hindsight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I mean, it wasn't a pleasant thing to do, you know, honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "a", "pleasant", "thing", "to", "do", ",", "you", "know", ",", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Have you managed to stay friends?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "managed", "to", "stay", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Yeah I mean, I think we both cared very deeply for each other.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "we", "both", "cared", "very", "deeply", "for", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How are you finding that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "finding", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm not the most outgoing fellow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "the", "most", "outgoing", "fellow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "What did you feel when all that bile was being spilled in your direction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "all", "that", "bile", "was", "being", "spilled", "in", "your", "direction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "You know, I think that it just -- when that first started with those type of people, I just kind of let it roll off my back.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "just", "--", "when", "that", "first", "started", "with", "those", "type", "of", "people", ",", "I", "just", "kind", "of", "let", "it", "roll", "off", "my", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120607pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do you and your stepmother have lively debates about this, Chaz?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "and", "your", "stepmother", "have", "lively", "debates", "about", "this", ",", "Chaz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "You know, we really -- we really don't.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "really", "--", "we", "really", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz?"]}}]